<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>WFHomies</title>
    <link href="https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies" />
    <updated>2022-04-21T13:00:21+01:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Ryan</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies</id>

    <entry>
        <title>The best monitors for working from home</title>
        <author>
            <name>Ryan</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies/the-best-monitors-for-working-from-home/"/>
        <id>https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies/the-best-monitors-for-working-from-home/</id>
            <category term="monitors"/>

        <updated>2022-04-21T13:00:21+01:00</updated>
            <summary>
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies/media/posts/1/monitors-feature-image.jpeg" alt="" />
                    Introduction: If you're like most people, you want to work from home as much as possible. But before you can do that, you need a good monitor to work on. Here are 9 of the best monitors for working from home. 1. ASUS VivoBook F510UA&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <img src="https://nobbyrn.github.io/wfhomies/media/posts/1/monitors-feature-image.jpeg" alt="" />
                <p>Introduction: If you're like most people, you want to work from home as much as possible. But before you can do that, you need a good monitor to work on. Here are 9 of the best monitors for working from home.</p>
<p>1. ASUS VivoBook F510UA is a powerful laptop that is perfect for students, professionals and anyone who needs a powerful laptop that is portable and affordable. This laptop has a durable design, excellent performance and great battery life.</p>
<p>2. Dell Inspiron 15 3000</p>
<p>Dell Inspiron 15 3000 is one of the best value monitors on the market. It has a great resolution for its price and comes with a lot of features that make it great for working from home. Some of the best features of this monitor include:</p>
<p>-It has a great resolution for its price, making it perfect for working with graphics or photos.</p>
<p>-It comes with a lot of features that make it great for working from home, including an adjustable stand and a VGA port.</p>
<p>4. Lenovo IdeaPad 320S-15IBR</p>
<p>Lenovo IdeaPad 320S-15IBR is a great choice for working from home. It has a large screen size and powerful specs that make it perfect for multitasking and online streaming. Plus, the backlit keyboard makes it easy to work in low light conditions.</p>
<p>5. Microsoft Surface Go 32GB with Windows 10 Pro (Certified Refurbished)</p>
<p>6. Acer Predator Helios 300 G3-571-6480 16GB DDR4 VRAM GT 710MX w/FreeDos 14" DisplayPort HDMI x 2 USB C Genuine PC Parts (Refurbished)</p>
<p>7. Apple iMac 21." 4K LED Retina Display Mid-Size Desktop Computer - Space Gray</p>
<p>8. Apple</p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
